Peter Fallon - Gallery Press collection, circa 1967-1998
Emory University
- Literary manuscripts, 1969-1998, Series 1; Boxes 1-111
  - Gallery Press author files, 1969-1998, Subseries 1.1; Boxes 1-85
    - Dunne, Seán, "The Abdication," [variant title of The Sheltered Nest] TS with corrections (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Dunne, Seán, The Sheltered Nest, Early Submission (1988), TS poems (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Dunne, Seán, The Sheltered Nest, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Dunne, Seán, The Sheltered Nest, Proofs with corrections (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Dunne, Seán, The Sheltered Nest, Proofs with corrections (photocopy) (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Dunne, Seán, The Sheltered Nest, TS with corrections (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Dunne, Seán, The Sheltered Nest, TS with editor's corrections (photocopy) (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Dunne, Seán, The Sheltered Nest, TS (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Dunne, Seán, "Ten Poems," TS (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Dunne, Seán, Time and the Island, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Dunne, Seán, Time and the Island, Proofs with corrections (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Dunne, Seán, Time and the Island, Proofs with corrections (Box OP8)
    - Dunne, Seán, Time and the Island, TS with corrections (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Durcan, Paul, Correspondence, 1975-1992 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Durcan, Paul, Miscellaneous (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Durcan, Paul, Other published works (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Durcan, Paul, TS poems (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Durcan, Paul, Teresa's Bar, Proofs with corrections (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Durcan, Paul, Teresa's Bar, Proofs with corrections (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Durcan, Paul, Teresa's Bar, Proofs with corrections (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Durcan, Paul, Teresa's Bar, Proofs with corrections (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Durcan, Paul, Teresa's Bar, Proofs (Box OP9)
    - Durcan, Paul, Teresa's Bar, TS with corrections (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Durcan, Paul, Teresa's Bar, TS (incomplete) (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Ennis, John, Book jacket material (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Ennis, John, Correspondence, 1974-1980 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Ennis, John, Correspondence, 1981-1988 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Ennis, John, Correspondence, 1989-1992 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Ennis, John, Miscellaneous (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Ennis, John, Other published works (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Ennis, John, TS poems (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Ennis, John, "Ray Daly," [variant title of The Burren Days: a poem] TS with corrections (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Ennis, John, "A Week in the Life of Ray Daly, Laboratory Technician," [variant title of The Burren Days: a poem] TS (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Ennis, John, The Burren Days: a poem, Proofs with corrections (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Ennis, John, The Burren Days: a poem, Proofs with corrections (Box OP10)
    - Ennis, John, The Burren Days: a poem, TS with corrections (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Ennis, John, The Burren Days: a poem, TS with corrections (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Ennis, John, The Burren Days: a poem, TS with corrections (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Ennis, John, "Decisions," TS (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Ennis, John, "Ballinabracky and Other Poems," [variant title of Dolmen Hill] TS with corrections (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Ennis, John, "Ballinabracky and Other Poems," [variant title of Dolmen Hill] TS with corrections (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Ennis, John, "Ballinabracky and Other Poems," [variant title of Dolmen Hill] TS with corrections (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Ennis, John, "Tribute to Anchises," [variant title of A Drink of Spring] TS (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Ennis, John, A Drink of Spring, TS with corrections (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Ennis, John, "Pale Venus," [variant title of "Fair City" (poem)] TS with corrections (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Ennis, John, "The Road to Patmos," [variant title of In a Green Shade] TS with corrections (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Ennis, John, "Fair City and Other Poems," [variant title of In a Green Shade (Dedalus, 1991)] TS (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Ennis, John, "Fair City and Other Poems," [variant title of In a Green Shade (Dedalus, 1991)] TS (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Ennis, John, "The Inward Spiral: Letter to Conle," [variant title of "Letter to Connla," published in Telling the Bees, 1995], TS with corrections (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Ennis, John, "The Inward Spiral: Letter to Conle," [variant title of "Letter to Connla," published in Telling the Bees, 1995] TS (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Ennis, John, Night on Hibernia, TS with corrections (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Ennis, John, Night on Hibernia, TS (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Ennis, John, Night on Hibernia, TS (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Ennis, John, "Shore-Dwellers," TS (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Fallon, Brian (ed.) [See: Fallon, Padraic Collected Poems] (Box -, Folder -)
    - Fallon, Padraic, Correspondence, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Fallon, Padraic, Miscellaneous (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Fallon, Padraic, Collected Poems, Book jacket material (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Fallon, Padraic, Collected Poems, Introduction (by Seamus Heaney) and Afterword (by Brian Fallon) (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Fallon, Padraic, Collected Poems, Proofs with corrections (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Friel, Brian [See: Hayes, Maurice (ed.), Flight Path] (Box -, Folder -)
    - Friel, Brian, Biographical (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Friel, Brian, Book jacket material (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Friel, Brian, Correspondence, 1978-1987 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Friel, Brian, Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Friel, Brian, Correspondence, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Friel, Brian, Correspondence, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Friel, Brian, Correspondence, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Friel, Brian, Correspondence, 1993-1996 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Friel, Brian, Correspondence, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Friel, Brian, Correspondence, undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Friel, Brian, Miscellaneous (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Friel, Brian, Aristocrats, Proofs with corrections (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Friel, Brian, Aristocrats, Proofs with corrections (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Friel, Brian, Aristocrats, TS with corrections (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Friel, Brian, Aristocrats, TS (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Friel, Brian, The Communication Cord, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Friel, Brian, The Communication Cord, Proofs with corrections (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Friel, Brian, The Communication Cord, TS with corrections (photocopy) (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Friel, Brian, The Enemy Within, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Friel, Brian, The Enemy Within, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Friel, Brian, The Enemy Within, Proofs with corrections (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Friel, Brian, The Enemy Within, Proofs with corrections (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Friel, Brian, The Enemy Within, Proofs with corrections (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Friel, Brian, The Enemy Within, Proofs (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Friel, Brian, Faith Healer, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Friel, Brian, Faith Healer, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Friel, Brian, Faith Healer, TS with corrections (photocopy) (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Friel, Brian, Famine Exodus, TS (photocopy) (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Friel, Brian, Farewell to Ardstraw, TS with corrections (photocopy) (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Friel, Brian, The Freedom of the City, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Friel, Brian, The Freedom of the City, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Friel, Brian, The Freedom of the City, Proofs with corrections (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Friel, Brian, The Freedom of the City, TS with corrections (photocopy) (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Friel, Brian, Friel Day, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Friel, Brian, Friel Day, TS with corrections (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Friel, Brian, The Gentle Island, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Friel, Brian, The Gentle Island, Proofs with corrections (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Friel, Brian, The Gentle Island, TS with corrections (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Friel, Brian, Give Me Your Answer, Do!, Miscellaneous (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Friel, Brian, Give Me Your Answer, Do!, Mock-ups (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Friel, Brian, Give Me Your Answer, Do!, Proofs with corrections (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Friel, Brian, Give Me Your Answer, Do!, Proofs with corrections (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Friel, Brian, Give Me Your Answer, Do!, TS with corrections (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Friel, Brian, Give Me Your Answer, Do!, TS (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Friel, Brian, Living Quarters, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Friel, Brian, Living Quarters, Proofs with corrections (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Friel, Brian, Living Quarters, TS with corrections (photocopy) (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Friel, Brian, The London Vertigo, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Friel, Brian, The London Vertigo, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Friel, Brian, The London Vertigo, Proofs with corrections (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Friel, Brian, The London Vertigo, TS with corrections (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Friel, Brian, Lovers, Proofs with corrections (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Friel, Brian, Lovers, Proofs with corrections (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Friel, Brian, Lovers, TS with corrections (photocopy) (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Friel, Brian, The Loves of Cass McGuire, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Friel, Brian, The Loves of Cass McGuire, TS with corrections (photocopy) (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Friel, Brian, Molly Sweeney, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Friel, Brian, Molly Sweeney, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Friel, Brian, Molly Sweeney, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Friel, Brian, Molly Sweeney, Proofs with corrections (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Friel, Brian, Molly Sweeney, TS with corrections (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Friel, Brian, Molly Sweeney, TS with corrections (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Friel, Brian, A Month in the Country: after Turgenev, Miscellaneous (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Friel, Brian, A Month in the Country: after Turgenev, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Friel, Brian, A Month in the Country: after Turgenev, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Friel, Brian, A Month in the Country: after Turgenev, Proofs with corrections (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Friel, Brian, A Month in the Country: after Turgenev, Proofs with corrections (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Friel, Brian, A Month in the Country: after Turgenev, TS with corrections (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Friel, Brian, Selected Stories, Miscellaneous (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Friel, Brian, Three Sisters, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Friel, Brian, Three Sisters, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Friel, Brian, Three Sisters, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Friel, Brian, Three Sisters, Proofs with corrections (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Friel, Brian, Three Sisters, Proofs with corrections (incomplete) (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Friel, Brian, Three Sisters, TS with corrections (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Friel, Brian, Volunteers, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Friel, Brian, Volunteers, Proofs with corrections (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Friel, Brian, Volunteers, Proofs with corrections (incomplete) (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Friel, Brian, Volunteers, TS with corrections (photocopy) (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Friel, Brian, Wonderful Tennessee, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Friel, Brian, Wonderful Tennessee, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Friel, Brian, Wonderful Tennessee, Mock-ups (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Friel, Brian, Wonderful Tennessee, Proofs with corrections (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Friel, Brian, Wonderful Tennessee, Proofs with corrections (photocopy) (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Friel, Brian, Wonderful Tennessee, TS with corrections (photocopy) (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Friel, Brian, Wonderful Tennessee, TS with corrections (photocopy) (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Friel, Brian, Wonderful Tennessee, TS with corrections (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Glavin, Anthony, Correspondence, 1988-1992 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Glavin, Anthony, The Wrong Side of the Alps, Miscellaneous (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Glavin, Anthony, The Wrong Side of the Alps, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Glavin, Anthony, The Wrong Side of the Alps, Mock-ups with corrections (incomplete) (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Glavin, Anthony, The Wrong Side of the Alps, Proofs with corrections (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Glavin, Anthony, The Wrong Side of the Alps, Proofs with corrections (photocopy) (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Glavin, Anthony, The Wrong Side of the Alps, TS with corrections (photocopy) (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Glavin, Anthony, The Wrong Side of the Alps, TS poems (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Glavin, Anthony, The Wrong Side of the Alps, TS with corrections (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Greacen, Robert, Correspondence, 1973-1993 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Greacen, Robert, Miscellaneous (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Greacen, Robert, A Garland for Captain Fox, TS with corrections (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Grennan, Eamon, Book jacket material (Box OP11)
    - Grennan, Eamon, Correspondence, 1981-1987 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Grennan, Eamon, Correspondence, 1988-1991 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Grennan, Eamon, Correspondence, 1992-1995, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Grennan, Eamon, Miscellaneous (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Grennan, Eamon, Other published works (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Grennan, Eamon, TS poems (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Grennan, Eamon, As If It Matters, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Grennan, Eamon, As If It Matters, Proofs with corrections (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Grennan, Eamon, As If It Matters, TS with corrections (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Grennan, Eamon, As If It Matters, TS with corrections (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Grennan, Eamon, "Tongues and Dust," [variant title of "For the Moment Standing"] TS with corrections (photocopy) (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Grennan, Eamon, "For the Moment Standing," TS with corrections (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Grennan, Eamon, "For the Moment Standing," TS (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Grennan, Eamon, Selected Poems of Giacomo Leopardi, Miscellaneous (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Grennan, Eamon, Selected Poems of Giacomo Leopardi, TS with corrections (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Grennan, Eamon, Selected Poems of Giacomo Leopardi, TS (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Grennan, Eamon, "Facing Silence," [variant title of So It Goes] TS with corrections (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Grennan, Eamon - "Natural Causes," [variant title of So It Goes] TS with corrections (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Grennan, Eamon, "Still Life with Waterfall," [variant title of So It Goes] TS with corrections (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Grennan, Eamon, So It Goes, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Grennan, Eamon, So It Goes, Proof with corrections (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Grennan, Eamon, So It Goes, TS with corrections (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Grennan, Eamon, So It Goes, TS with corrections (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Grennan, Eamon, So It Goes, TS with corrections (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Grennan, Eamon, What Light There Is, Mock-ups (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Grennan, Eamon, What Light There Is, Proofs with corrections (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Grennan, Eamon, What Light There Is, Proofs with corrections (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Grennan, Eamon, What Light There Is, Proofs with corrections (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Grennan, Eamon, What Light There Is, Proofs with corrections (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Grennan, Eamon, What Light There Is, Proofs with corrections (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Grennan, Eamon, What Light There Is, TS poems with corrections (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Grennan, Eamon, What Light There Is, TS with corrections (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Grennan, Eamon, What Light There Is, TS with corrections (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Grennan, Eamon, "Coming to Attention," [variant title of Wildly for Days] TS (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Grennan, Eamon, Wildly for Days, Book jacket material (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Grennan, Eamon, Wildly for Days, Galley (Box OP12)
    - Grennan, Eamon, Wildly for Days, Galley with corrections (Box OP13)
    - Grennan, Eamon, Wildly for Days, TS with corrections (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Grennan, Eamon, Wildly for Days, TS with corrections (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Groarke, Vona, Biographical (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Groarke, Vona, Correspondence, 1992-1995 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Groarke, Vona, Other published works (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Groarke, Vona, TS poems (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Groarke, Vona, Shale, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Groarke, Vona, Shale, Proofs with corrections (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Groarke, Vona, Shale, Proofs with corrections (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Groarke, Vona, Shale, TS with corrections (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Groarke, Vona, Shale, TS with corrections (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Groarke, Vona, Shale, TS (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Hardie, Kerry, Correspondence, 1994-1997 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Hardie, Kerry, Other published works (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Hardie, Kerry, A Furious Place, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Hardie, Kerry, A Furious Place, Proofs with corrections (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Hardie, Kerry, A Furious Place, Proofs (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Hardie, Kerry, A Furious Place, TS poems with corrections (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Hardie, Kerry, A Furious Place, TS with corrections (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Hardie, Kerry, A Furious Place, TS with corrections (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Hardie, Kerry, A Furious Place, TS with corrections (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Hartnett, Michael [See: Hayes, Maurice (ed.), Flight Path] (Box -, Folder -)
    - Hartnett, Michael, Book jacket material (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Hartnett, Michael, Correspondence, 1975-1986 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Hartnett, Michael, Correspondence, 1987-1994 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Hartnett, Michael, MS and TS poems (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Hartnett, Michael, MS poems (notebook) (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Hartnett, Michael, Other published works (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Hartnett, Michael, Adarca Broic, Book jacket material (Box OP83)
    - Hartnett, Michael, Adarca Broic, Book jacket material (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Hartnett, Michael, A Farewell to English, Mock-ups (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Hartnett, Michael, A Farewell to English, Proofs with corrections (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Hartnett, Michael, A Farewell to English, Proofs with corrections (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Hartnett, Michael, A Farewell to English, Proofs with corrections (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Hartnett, Michael, A Farewell to English, Proofs (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Hartnett, Michael, A Farewell to English, TS with corrections (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Hartnett, Michael, Haicéad, MS with corrections (photocopy) (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Hartnett, Michael, Haicéad, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Hartnett, Michael, Haicéad, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Hartnett, Michael, Haicéad, Proofs with corrections (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Hartnett, Michael, Haicéad, TS with corrections (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Hartnett, Michael, Haicéad, TS with corrections (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Hartnett, Michael, The Killing of Dreams, MS (photocopy) (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Hartnett, Michael, The Killing of Dreams, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Hartnett, Michael, The Killing of Dreams, TS with corrections (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Hartnett, Michael, A Necklace of Wrens, MS with corrections (photocopy) (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Hartnett, Michael, A Necklace of Wrens, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Hartnett, Michael, A Necklace of Wrens, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Hartnett, Michael, A Necklace of Wrens, Proofs with corrections (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Hartnett, Michael, A Necklace of Wrens, Proofs with corrections (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Hartnett, Michael, A Necklace of Wrens, Proofs with corrections (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Hartnett, Michael, A Necklace of Wrens, Proofs with corrections (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Hartnett, Michael, A Necklace of Wrens, Proofs with corrections (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Hartnett, Michael, A Necklace of Wrens, Proofs with corrections (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Hartnett, Michael, A Necklace of Wrens, Proofs (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Hartnett, Michael, A Necklace of Wrens, TS with corrections (photocopy) (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Hartnett, Michael, "The Fate of Himself: Selected Poems of Dáibhí Ó Bruadair," [variant title of Ó Bruadair: Selected Poems of Dáibhí Ó Bruadair] TS with corrections [in Irish] (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Hartnett, Michael, Ó Bruadair: Selected Poems of Dáibhí Ó Bruadair, Proofs with corrections (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Hartnett, Michael, Ó Bruadair: Selected Poems of Dáibhí Ó Bruadair, TS with corrections (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Hartnett, Michael, Poems to Younger Women, MS and typecript with corrections (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Hartnett, Michael, Poems to Younger Women, Proofs with corrections (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Hartnett, Michael, Poems to Younger Women, Proofs with corrections (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Hartnett, Michael, Poems to Younger Women, TS with corrections (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Hartnett, Michael, Prisoners, Proofs (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Hartnett, Michael, The Purge [Beaver Row Press, 1989], MS and TS [in English and Irish] (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Hartnett, Michael, Secular Prayers, MS with corrections (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Hartnett, Michael, Selected and New Poems, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Hartnett, Michael, Selected and New Poems, Proofs with corrections (photocopy) (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Hartnett, Michael, Selected and New Poems, TS with corrections (photocopy) (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Hartnett, Michael, Sonnets from the Dark Side of the Mind, MS with corrections (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Harvey, Francis, Book jacket material (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Harvey, Francis, Correspondence, 1973-1992 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Harvey, Francis, Correspondence, 1993-1995 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Harvey, Francis - Miscellaneous (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Harvey, Francis- TS poem (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Harvey, Francis, In the Light of the Stones, TS with corrections (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Harvey, Francis, The Rainmakers, Proofs with corrections (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Harvey, Francis, The Rainmakers, Proofs with corrections (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Harvey, Francis, The Rainmakers, Proofs with corrections (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Harvey, Francis, The Rainmakers, TS with corrections (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Hayes, Maurice (ed.), Flight Path, Evan Boland submission and correspondence (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Hayes, Maurice (ed.), Flight Path, Hubert Butler submission and correspondence (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Hayes, Maurice (ed.), Flight Path, Austin Clarke submission and correspondence (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Hayes, Maurice (ed.), Flight Path, Seamus Deane submission and correspondence (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Hayes, Maurice (ed.), Flight Path, Brian Friel submission and correspondence (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Hayes, Maurice (ed.), Flight Path, Michael Hartnett submission and correspondence (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Hayes, Maurice (ed.), Flight Path, Seamus Heaney submission and correspondence (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Hayes, Maurice (ed.), Flight Path, Aidan Higgins submission and correspondence (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Hayes, Maurice (ed.), Flight Path, John B. Keane submission and correspondence (Box 33, Folder 11)